 [
    {
      "id": 1,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",
      "question": "He finally ___ smoking after 10 years.",
      "options": ["gave up", "gave out", "gave off", "gave in"],
      "answer": "gave up"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "I’m really ___ with my noisy neighbors.",
      "options": ["fed up", "taken up", "put out", "broken down"],
      "answer": "fed up"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "The meeting was ___ because the manager was sick.",
      "options": ["called off", "put up", "taken away", "carried on"],
      "answer": "called off"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "He takes ___ his grandfather. They both love gardening.",
      "options": ["after", "over", "off", "up"],
      "answer": "after"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "She’s very ___ — she never gives up easily.",
      "options": ["determined", "polite", "lazy", "shy"],
      "answer": "determined"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "Which word means 'not allowed by law'?",
      "options": ["illegal", "impossible", "impolite", "immoral"],
      "answer": "illegal"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "The opposite of 'increase' is ___.",
      "options": ["decrease", "expand", "improve", "develop"],
      "answer": "decrease"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "If you want to ___ weight, you should eat less sugar.",
      "options": ["lose", "miss", "drop", "fall"],
      "answer": "lose"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "He made a very ___ impression during the interview.",
      "options": ["positive", "usual", "noisy", "angry"],
      "answer": "positive"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
       "level": "B1",
  "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "She looked ___ after the baby while her sister was away.",
      "options": ["after", "for", "up", "out"],
      "answer": "after"
    }
  ]

